# exander Mazurenko

Currently based in Istanbul, Turkey

🛘 +79818482332 | 💌 feelsknight@gmail.com | 🏕 alexmazurenko.vercel.app | 🖸 stonekite | 🛅 alexandermazurenko



# **Summary**

Hard-working and always curious developer with over 3 years of experience and excellent soft skills to boot. Worked with large-scale applications used in complex business processes by people all around the globe. Eager and able to learn new things as well as teach others what I know. Besides coding and video games, I love art, languages and all things humanitarian; also my dog, a shiba named Yuki — remember to ask to see him at the interview, he's very cute!

# Work Experience

#### **Bright Data (PaaS proxy, data collection)**

Netanya, Israel (Remote)

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Apr. 2022

- · Updating control panel components and backend services with React, Sass, Node, MongoDB, Figma.
- Integrating third party services on both sides of the stack such as Zendesk, Monday, reCaptcha.
- Developing validators for our third party service integrations.
- Fully asynchronous remote workflow with teammates throughout EU and US timezones.

#### innoscripta (SaaS ERP, businesses index)

Munich, Germany (Hybrid)

Mar. 2021 - Apr. 2022

• Developing new components and pages with React, Redux, Sass, PostgreSQL, Figma.

- Re-implementing existing components from the ground up (React 16.8 migrations, major product updates, etc.).
- Dynamic startup environment close contact with teammates, back-end and design teams.

#### NSYS Group (SaaS ERP, mobile diagnostics solution)

Jan. 2020 - Mar. 2021

JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

- Developing new ERP products with .NET 5, Vue, Sass, Bootstrap, MSSQL, Figma.
- Performing legacy code refactoring, .NET version migrations and DB migrations.
- · Using and setting up pipelines utilizing Docker and gulp.

# Skills

### **Front End**

PRIMARILY REACT + TS

- JavaScript (ECMAScript 6+, TypeScript)
- React.js, Next.js, Gatsby.js
- Redux, react-redux, redux-saga
- Sass, Tailwind, styled-components, emotion

#### **Back End**

PRIMARILY NODE + MONGO

- · Node.js, Express.js, Next.js, Sequelize, Knex.js, Prisma
- · Python, Django, Bottle, Selenium, BeautifulSoup, PIL
- · MongoDB, PostgreSQL

#### Other

HARD AND SOFT

- git, Docker, docker-compose, Figma, Linux (I use Arch BTW)
- C2 English (IELTS 2020), native Russian, learning Spanish
- Good communicator, team player, explainer and learner, friend-maker:)
- · Probably not going to use this in my work but I'm obsessed with functional programming and ClojureScript in particular at the moment

# Education

**ITMO University** 

B.Sc. Computer Science

Saint Petersburg, Russia

Sep. 2018 - Jun. 2020 (Incomplete)

ALEXANDER MAZURENKO · RÉSUMÉ